We're about to pick a badass right now.
Welcome to the brotherhood.
>> It's on y'all. The Washington commander
select Jaden Daniel.
>> Jaden Daniel is such a revelation.
>> John Carly Jr.
>> Someone hooked you and that was Alan
Peters.
>> A+ I'll leave with the headline. Home
run after home run.
The command center live draft special is
presented by SeatGeek, the official
primary ticketing partner of the
Washington Commanders and Northwest
Stadium. Find tickets to commanders
games, concerts, and more. SeatGeek.
Welcome to our command center draft
special presented by Segeek. The most
disruptive day ticket. A ticket that
works. Expect the expected CG. The Steel
City is buzzing for the start of the
2026 NFL draft. And the Game Day crew
and I are out here in Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania as we await the start of
round one. And of course, the best fans
in the NFL are here with us in spirit as
they stand by out of Northwest Stadium
for the Commanders Draft Party. Heavy
game day energy out there on the home
field. Much love to our Commanders
family. But it's not just me and these
greatl looking gentlemen right here out
in Pittsburgh. We're all hands on deck
for this year's draft. We got the get
loud crew out at the party site. We got
the studio crew in there looking good.
Logan put on his best casket. Boy,
looking clean over there, fellas.
>> Before we get to them though, it's all
about us right here out in Pittsburgh.
The game day crew back together again.
Fellas, it's wild to think this is our
third year doing this together, man. How
y'all feeling?
>> Feeling good, man. Now, this is a day
for a lot of guys to look forward to.
Uh, this is going to change their lives,
be an opportunity for them to go out
there and live out some childhood
dreams, you know. Uh, I I say this
though, whatever you've done thus far,
forget about that. You got to do a
little bit more to stick and say,
>> it's super exciting, man. I think one of
the things that I'm looking forward to
is just seeing some of these guys walk
across that stage, you know, and
actually say, I can now say, I've done
it, you know, I'm here. I remember my
time. I was nervous as crap. I was I was
sitting there biting my nails and now I
get a joy of watching everybody else
live out that experience. And it's
better from this seat than it was from
that seat. But at the same time, I was
excited once I did hear my name. And
fellas, what what makes Command Center
better than any other show in my opinion
is the fact that y'all have done this
before. Y'all have memories at the
draft. B, I'm going to start with you
cuz you were drafted and watched it.
When you go back and think about young
Brian Mitchell, man, waiting to
accomplish his dream, young Louisiana
boy, man, what brings to mind when you
think about your draft experience?
That's an opportunity, you know, uh it's
something I always wanted to do and uh
just to get that opportunity. I didn't
care what team it was. Didn't care what
round it was going to be. I knew if I
got into the training camp with
somebody, they going to know who Brian
Mitchell was. And I think that's what I
want every player to understand. First
round draft pick, seventh round draft
pick, undrafted free agent, you have an
opportunity to go out there and prove to
somebody what you're capable of. You
know, the guys that get drafted higher
has a better chance, but you can change
somebody's mind about yourself. And I
think I went out there, that's all I
wanted was an opportunity to prove who I
really was.
>> And Tana, before you wore a first round
pick for the Jets, you were a walk-on,
man. You had to earn everything you got.
What was the draft like for you knowing
that, man, I had to scry and crawl just
to get here. And now I'm being
considered a first round pick, man. That
had been pretty cool.
>> You know, I felt good, but I like I said
before, I kid you not, I don't, you
know, I still wasn't just fully there in
my head, in my mentals. you know, my my
my focus was still like, okay, once this
thing is over, I got to get back to work
because now I want to make sure that
this team knows that they have the
player that they thought they had, you
know, that that who they picked is the
guy who I am, you know, and so like I
was I was one of those guys. I was I was
eager to get out there and show them
that I'm the draft pick. I'm that first
round draft choice that you selected.
>> Dang. 14 years later, man, what a career
it was here with some great guys. But
again, it's not just us here in
Pittsburgh. We got coverage all across
the DMV. Let's check in on our
Commanders draft party out of Northwest
Stadium. Our Get Loud crew of Fred
Smoot, Mike Jinx, and the boy Sean
Springs even pulled up out there to be
amongst the fans. Fellas, I know y'all
are just as excited as us.
>> I know y'all are just as excited as us.
I know y'all are just as excited as us.
>> How you guys doing?
>> Yeah. You ready for tonight's draft?
>> Let's go
Springs Fred Smooth.
>> Let's do it. Let's do it. tonight.
>> I know everybody's ready to have a good
time because I heard someone say right
here in front, "Smoot, you owe me a
beer." I'm like, "Oh, already."
>> Hey, I owe everybody a beer, baby. Put
it on this time. Put on the side.
>> The energy out here is incredible. It's
only going to ramp up. And what was it
like coming into the stand? This has
been an upgrade. Last year, we were
hanging out in the bar.
>> Hey, we real now.
>> We got the band, we got the music, we
got floaties, we got all type of stuff
going on. And the weather.
>> No, no, no. You can feel the energy
because guess what? We got that real
burgundy gold back. We got our new stuff
back. It's the beginning of taking us
back to the great days. And you can only
do that by being genuine. And genuinely
right now, the burgundy and gold is back
in the NFL.
>> Yeah.
>> We haven't got those sweet black
alternate uniforms.
>> A there's
>> I see the blacks out there.
>> Yeah.
>> So, you were at the uniform reveal,
Fred. You got a special jersey out
there, right? You got it with you. Whoa.
>> Oh, man.
>> Let me show y'all the new new.
>> Huh? Hey. Hey.
>> Let me show you the new new.
>> Can you give us some plays in it? Can
you give us some plays?
>> I ain't got no more plays. I ain't got
no more plays.
>> Well, we can't leave our guy Sean
empty-handed. So, we got him a jerk,
too.
>> Hey,
>> there we go.
>> There we go.
>> Hey, we can make some things happen.
Smooth. We might need to come back. 27
and two back. That's right. Let's go.
>> Right here, baby.
>> Let's go.
>> If you want a new jersey, you can get it
at Fanatics. And we're going to have a
new member wearing this burgundy and
gold tonight. So,
>> which player We'll start with you, Sean,
since you just got your fresh new
jersey. But which player do you think
has the most value in this draft?
>> Well, when you look I I have to go with
the guy Jeremiah Love. Show me big love.
Jeremiah Love was just athletic, smooth,
best offensive player in the draft.
Mendoza is going to go probably number
one, but Jeremiah Love, you talking
about Instant Impact. Think Jir Gibbs,
>> think Bean Robinson, think McCarthy,
he's in that mode. He's the type of guy
not only can you hand the ball off to
him, he can take a 60 at any time, but
he can catch out of the back field. He
is a nightmare. He can create a matchup
on linebackers, safeties, and anyone.
Give JD5 some weapons and a kid the kid
like that can go. Blue Foot. The thing
about it is he could be the best running
back in this draft and the best receiver
in this draft. That's the crazy thing
about his freaking athleticism.
>> Yeah, he's pretty good athlete.
>> And Smoon, I know you're going
defensively and of course with the
Buckeye that Sean loves.
>> Well, you know, you're going to think
about it. I don't know if y'all seen
Sunny Styles at the combine, but I'm
talking about a complete monster. I'm
talking about a complete dog. I'm
talking about Fred Warner mixed with
Brian Erlacer. I'm talking about
somebody that can get sideline to
sideline. Somebody that can check tight
end. Somebody that can check running
back. Somebody that can run the middle
of the field. Somebody that can swap
that paint. All right. When I say Sunday
style, you know you getting the animal.
All right. Listen to me. Listen to me.
He ain't even reached his ceiling.
That's the great thing about it. It's
room for him to grow. If you ain't
excited about Sunny Styles, you might
need to check your post. That's what you
need to do.
>> Are you ready to donate to the Church of
Fred Smooth?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Let's go.
>> Let's go. So, we were talking right
before this show came on, which is
unlike a lot of years. We know Mendoza
is going one to the Raids, but after
that, it's a real crapshoot. They don't
know.
>> It is wide open. It's never been a draft
that I've seen in the last 20 years like
this.
>> You never know what guy could go next.
And there's so many great guys from Bane
to Reese to Downs to I mean, you just
think about it and you just never
absolutely know. This is the first time
it's actually a real crapshoot.
>> Well, here going to think about it. I
think the draft starts at three. When
Arizona Cardinals are on the clock, I
think that's when the draft started.
After that, Fernando already you you
feel confident about it. I feel
comfortable about the number two pick
with the Jets. I feel like they going
Arl Reese. And I think the draft starts
with the Cardinals. And the thing about
the Cardinals, we know they'll mess a
draft up. Like, so at the end of the
day, it is some blue chip guys here. But
Tennessee is the biggest threat to
Jeremiah Love. The best thing going for
us with them is Robert Salah is the head
coach and does he see Sunonny Styles and
and be forced to draft him? I think
that's gonna be the big question.
>> Well, where does David Bailey fit for
you? Because he's excellent.
>> He's too, right? I I thought
>> I know, but talked about Smoot and I
talked about before this talking about
the Jets need somebody who can rush the
pastor. There is no doubt that their kid
is the best pure pass rusher in the
draft.
>> You're right about that. He is the best
pure pass rusher in the draft. And
that's why I say if the Jets smart, they
take him realizing they got another pick
in the first round because he's a
surefire thing at the end. Our Reese
been a stand up linebacker. He been a
chasing pursuit guy. He been a guy that
did a lot, but at the end of the day,
I'm going to go with David Bailey
because he's the surefire thing when it
comes to rushing the pass.
>> We're just getting started on our
coverage here in the DMV. You guys going
to have a good time tonight with us.
>> DC, great job starting things off. We're
going to send it back up to you in
Pittsburgh.
Fellas, it's looking like a good time
down at Northwest Stadium. Now, there
are some big decisions to be made
tonight for general manager, Adam
Peters, and company back in Ashburg. And
earlier this week, I had a chance to
catch up with the general manager ahead
of this year's draft and asked him about
this 2026 draft class that's loaded with
talent. Check it out.
>> You talk about the draft and there's a
lot of talent in this draft all through
it. But when you look at just the pool
as a whole, this talent that's in the
draft this year, what does it make you
feel like is one of the best prospect
evaluators in the game?
>> Um, you know, I I think I'd start with,
you know, where we're sitting at pick
seven. And I feel really good about, you
know, getting a really good player
there. So, I think that's that's the the
first first part of it. And there's so
many good players at so many different
spots. You you could really fill in the
whole team and see there's going to be a
good player at any position, which is
cool. So, we can just go ahead and pick
who we think is best. But, you can
always find the gyms late in the draft.
And and that's where our our college
scouts, you know, they make their hey on
day three. And they've done a great job
these last couple years of really um
setting the table and really letting us
know who they really like. You know, not
just, you know, on the tape, but what
what makes these guys tick, you know,
the type of people they are, the the
human beings, how much they love
football, teammate, and all the
different things that make you a great
pro. So that process, although you get
more attention on the first round pick,
that that part's my favorite.
AP has done an excellent job in his
first three years. You can catch our
full interview on the Commander YouTube
channel, of course, after the draft.
Now, let's take a look at who the
experts have mocked to Washington at
number seven. Bookie Brooks of
edible.com has a taking safety Caleb DS
out of Ohio State. Charles Davis out of
CBS has us taking linebacker Sunny
Styles out of Ohio State. And once
again, Ohio State. Mel Kyper out of ESPN
has us taking Cardell Tate. Let's send
it over to our radio crew out in the
studio. Like I said, we got all hands on
deus. Logan Paulson, London Fletcher,
and Bram Weinstein. Y'all take it away.
>> All right. Thanks, Brian. Welcome into
the Big Bear AI Command Center studio.
Radio crew back together.
>> That's right, man. It's good to see you
guys. Really good to see you guys.
London you guys, man.
>> London Fletcher, Logan Paulson, Bram
Weinstein. Who hasn't been mocked to us?
>> I mean, nobody. I mean, everybody's
maybe you.
>> Me? But today, actually, I'm at the
airport getting off the plane and the
guy was like, "Hey, man, you London
Fletcher." I was like, "Yeah." He's
like,
>> you know, you think you're going to come
back this year? I was like, "Listen, I
said, man, the way my back and my knee
feel and and this looks they they got
real problems if I'm coming back to
play."
>> It might be someone who plays like you.
It's going to be a banner day for Ohio
State and one of those players could
come to the Commanders, right?
>> Yeah, absolutely. I mean, Caleb Downs,
Sunny Styles, all these guys. Let's take
a look real quick at these guys.
>> Oh, yeah. You know, I love my Buckeyes.
>> I know. Yeah, you're Buckeyes. That's
exactly right. So, we're going to talk
with our guy Caleb DS. He's off the
screen up here at the top right behind
you, Fletch. Kind of in this onehole
look. And I don't know, Fletch, if
there's a more instinctive football
player in this draft class, man.
Watching down, reading the quarterback's
eyes. I'm going to rip the ball in this
guy's hand. Had on the football.
>> Trigger trigger right now. But you you
said it a more instinctive football
player. He is the most extinctive
football player. Intelligent. Think
think about this. He was a freshman that
started for Nick Saving in Alabama. The
only one in the history of Alabama
football. But you see the explosiveness.
He caused two forced fumbles in that
ball game. I love the versatility also
of a Caleb Donald.
>> Yeah. I mean nickels safety kind of box
linebacker. And again, you see him line
up. So he's playing the whole player
here. Come to the next clip and he's
playing this Tampa two. They're going to
get in this kind of two shell here. He's
gonna run the middle right down the pipe
here. And watch him just read this out.
Fletch. And honestly, Fletch just
reminds me of you when you played,
right? Playing that Tampa player.
They're trying to get him to bite the
cheese, take these clear out, clear out
that zone. And he just says, "I know
what this is. I'm going to sit right
here and make this play on this
football."
>> This is teaching tape of how you play
what you consider the whole player in
cover two with the great vision of the
quarterback and understanding route
recognition and then driving downhill
and making the interception. I've seen
so many often times you'll see guys be
there to make the play
>> uh drop the interception things like
that and the wherewithal to know hey
that seal that victory get down he's
just such a smart football player
>> and so that's one of the guys and then
the other guy is is K is um Sunny Styles
man and watch him here he's kind up in
the A gap this reminds me of stuff that
Dante Jones does we're in the A gap
we're disguising coverage we're getting
out to our spots and the amount of
ground he's able to cover here speaks to
his length and his athletic profile
>> well when you're 6'5 and you run 446.
You could do this type of thing and then
arrive violently. You think about this.
What does Dad Quinn talk about? Arriving
violently. I think that's arriving
violently right there on that
>> 100% man. And that's how you get the
ball out, too, man. So, I love to see
that. The physicality, the movement
skills, and everyone says, "Oh, he's not
Arll Ree. He can't rush." Man, I see a
guy who can rush the passer here. Watch
him. He's going to beat the tackle. This
guy was drafted by Philadelphia last
year. He gets this win. I think there's
more flexibility to his game than people
think.
>> A lot of flexibility, versatility here.
you we saw the play of him in coverage
now rushing off the edge and you
mentioned beating a tackle and this is
Texas this is not you know Ohio
University or Acra University this is
Texas and he's getting dipping ripping
and getting that sack that's the great
versatility that a sunny Styles brings
to the football uh team
>> and I think I see shades of like you
know can we line him up multiple spots a
nice chest piece for the defense and so
obviously can pressure can cover can run
both those guys are great in and around
line of scrimmage a guy that's moving
away from line of scrimmage is Mansour
Lane from LSU. And I don't know if
there's a better cover rep than this
right here, Fletch. Like, I mean, this
is excellent, man. Look at these feet.
Look at how patient he is. Got to love
this type of football player.
>> Oh, man. Sammy Davis Jr. would be
impressed with those feet. He's tap
dancing with that receiver right out
there. I mean, that receiver and I love,
you mentioned the patience, staying
staying on the top field shoulder,
upfield shoulder, not panicking at all,
getting his head around and being in
position. Hey, if you're going to try to
throw the back shoulder, I can defend
that. If you try to go deep, this is
textbook. I'm glad you said back. I'm
glad you said not panicking flesh
because I think this next clip shows
that also, right? Like he's a guy that
is so confident in the indicators that
are out. 5 yards, 10 yards. Like he this
guy is trying to sell go all day, every
day up the line, really sell it. He
trusts his speed. He's able to sit down
on this and then play the football. I
mean, competitive, physical, love it,
right?
>> But what I love, run this back.
>> Yeah. What we got
>> the change of direction. Watch this.
He's he's he's going uphill. Bam. That
that right there, right? That's why you
do that for that 510 five drill. When
you see that type of change of
direction, this is a he is a great cover
corner.
>> So, Brand, that's three guys right there
that I pretty excited about.
>> Uh Delane, Silver Spring native. So,
coming home. Caleb G, you mentioned
Alabama, first freshman ever to lead the
Alabama program in tackles. That's
before he went to Ohio State. And guess
who knows Sunny Styles really well? Him.
He played with his dad.
>> I did. I did.
>> Do you feel old?
>> No.
that Super Bowl champion with the with
the Sunny's dad, Lorenzo D. We played
with the Rams.
>> And the crazy part is they got a lot of
other options to think about as well as
the draft is about to start as we send
it back to Pittsburgh.
>> Shout out to our radio crew out in
Ashurn. And we are out here in
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. You see that
draft clock? That means it's just 40
minutes until the 2026 NFL draft starts.
Before we get to that, we still have a
lot to get into because I have two
premier offensive players in the day
when they played for Washington. So
fellas, let's talk about these offensive
weapons cuz so many people have been
mocked to us including offenses. Look at
wide receiver B Mitch. I'm going to
start with you. Tanner, you can add in
as well. Got a guy like Carnell Tape,
Jordan Tyson. Two big guys, 6'2, a lot
of size on there. Both of them have been
mocked to us. Both of them fit with us
in different ways. How do you see them
either match it in our offense? Well,
when you look at Cornell Tate, I think
many people look at his 40 time and you
see a guy run 453. If he ran 448, nobody
would be saying anything, but you're
talking about that big of a gap. But he
when he comes in at 6'2, he's shown when
he was at Ohio State, he can run past
people. Okay? I always tell people,
Jerry Rice ran a 46. I saw him run past
4 threes all the time. You know, he has
that ability. He can also go up and get
the ball over people. He's a a guy when
he had that tough catch, he could catch
the ball over guys. You look at another
kid like uh Jordan Tyson. Jordan Tyson
is very twitchy. He's a guy who get in
and out of routes, but he has those
injuries that's been kind of hampering
him a little bit, which you hope he can
overcome.
>> No doubt. You know, uh Con to me, he's
the most when I'm looking at receivers
in this draft, he's the the to me the
most pro ready wide receiver in this
draft. Smooth route runner. Come from uh
wide receiver U. Ohio State seem like
every year they put on a new wide
receiver. and and he he has a savviness
about him that it seems to me that he
could come in and be on any, you know,
pro roster right now and be productive.
Uh Jordan Tyson is just like being Mitch
talked about very twitchy, uber
talented. I mean, he's he might be the
most dynamic out of all these guys. You
have a couple other guys probably in the
later rounds, you can probably compare
him to, but from first round wide
receivers, he is explosive. He's one of
those guys that when you see him on the
field, you know he about to do
something. But the only problem and the
only worry that worries me and worry
everybody else, can we keep him healthy?
So I think when you kind of compare
those things, that's why Tay kind of,
you know, you know, favors a little more
of being a guy to go. But I think both
of these guys can fit in our system, not
really knowing what we're going to be
yet, but just knowing how we want to get
the ball out
>> and be there's so many interviews,
there's so many rumors, right? But we
heard Tate say recently, Jada say he
want me. Yeah.
>> Does that carry a little bit of weight
when your quarterback is vouching for a
guy?
>> You know, if what I think Jaden is a is
a great guy.
>> Yeah.
>> And and if you talk to guys, you say
that. What if he comes here?
>> You know, you don't want to be saying,
"I don't want you." But the ultimate
thing is I think Jaden looks at Cornell
Tate and look at his ability and
understand that dude can help me.
>> And I think that's the ultimate thing
you want. You want to see cuz when I
look at uh roster building right now,
receivers are more valuable than than
when it comes to running back. And when
you look at our receiver room, you start
thinking about a guy coming in now who
could take over two or three years from
now.
>> You know, those things are something
that you go into and a Cornell Tate,
Jordan Tyson, a Mai Lemon, those guys
can be that guy that come in here and
fill that void.
>> And Tana Beich mentioned the wide
receiver room. A lot of young talent
bringing guys back in like Dei Brown.
There's guys out there that are willing
to prove it. And he talked about the
priority of getting a receiver. However,
this is widely considered to be a very
deep wide receiver draft. Knowing what
we have in house already, are you more
willing to say, you know what, let's try
to go get a wide receiver in the late
rounds and maybe address some other
positions.
>> I think this one of the first years I've
ever watched where you get a guy in Tate
that was arguably, well, I can't say
arguably, he was the second best on his
team,
>> but coming out into the draft that he's
going to go overall first wide receiver.
They have him potentially being the
first wide receiver taken in this draft.
So when I say that, it it leads me to
think that watching all the other guys,
all the other bodies of work, we
probably can't afford to kind of get a
guy later. You know what I mean? Whether
we take somebody's pick and and move
back in the first round or even, you
know, take a pick, move back in the
first round, still go somewhere else
with that pick and then get a second
round pick, you know, with that move.
Maybe we It's a lot of talent out there
at receiver. And I don't think none of
these guys separate theirelves from each
other, you know, like some of the other
draft classes. So, um, it's just my view
on it because I feel like we have we
have a dynamic class of wide receiver
coming out this year, but I don't think
you can go wrong whether you'll get a
guy early or wait to get somebody late
in the later rounds. And BB, we're
running out of time, so we got to do
this quick. But I can't move forward
from offense without bringing up
Jeremiah Love, right? Everybody's
salivating, hoping Jeremiah Love, you
heard Fred said it out there. He said,
"Hey, Titans might be our worst enemy
tonight, man." How does a guy like
Jeremiah Love fit with a guy like Jaden
Dames?
>> Uh, I think Jeremiah Love fits in any
offense. And and the thing we saw last
year, Jaden has the mindset he has to be
Superman a lot of times. You get a guy
on the football field like a Golov, he
doesn't have to be that. He can take a
lot of pressure off of him. Also can
take pressure off our defense.
>> Now, let's flip it over to the defensive
side of the ball and look at some of the
prospects experts have mocked to
Washington. Again, so many players have
been mocked to us. A couple of Ohio
State Buckeyes and linebacker Sunny
Styles and safety Caleb DS. and edges
linked to Washington throughout the mock
draft include guys like Ruben Bane. So
much potential, so much talent in the
top 10. Let's send it back to the crib
out in Northwest Stadium with the Get
Loud crew standing by to talk about some
of these defensive players.
Hey,
hey, hey.
fellas, they enjoyed us talking offense
so much. Let's talk a little more about
this offense as we experience some
technical difficulties. You know, we try
to do these big draft shows for y'all
and it's cuz y'all the best fans in the
NFL, but sometimes when you're trying
new things, there's a little bit of
hiccup. So, we're going to chill here
till our guys are ready for us to move
forward. Now, again, let's talk about
Jeremiah Love. Let's get back to it cuz
Tanner, you didn't get to speak on him.
Just an impressive specimen. I think I
heard Fred say that. He said, "This guy
could be the best receiver and the best
running back." Man, how happy would you
be to get a talent like that on this
offense?
>> You know, I would be um I would be
ecstatic. I think one of the things
about what we've seen last year that
took place is we don't want to see, you
know, our quarterback put in those
situations where he has to be the guy
all the time. He has to go out there
and, you know, will will us into victory
because we're depleted at the wide
receive position or we don't have
somebody in the back field that we can
just, you know, lean on for the for for
half of the game. And I think when you
have a back like, you know, uh, Love and
if he was ever, you know, to, you know,
we was ever fortunate enough to have him
in this draft and and and pick him up in
our our first pick, you know, I think
right then and there, it just sets us
apart in this division. I think when you
have those two talents together, you p
two talents together, what defense, you
know, want to sit there and be worried
about Terry on the outside, Love in the
back field, and Jaden Daniels in the
back field. So, I think when you have
and then you have those tight ends to
worry about. So, um, he would just set
us apart, man. And it it's just one of
those things if you can sit here right
now and think about it, if it comes
true, man, might be a sight to see.
>> And you look at a guy like Jeremiah Love
and again, you talk about that pairing
of him with Jaden Daniels and you say
this could help Jaden Daniels in that
year three, even though year two was a
little bit up and down. How valuable is
a running back like that for a
quarterback, B Mitch? Well, I think
people look at running backs today, and
I know the game is not about running the
football, but when you have a legitimate
running back who can take that pressure
off your quarterback, who's going to
make them be worried, they going to
bring somebody else down into the box to
try and stop them. Now, you get a lot of
one-on-one matchups. And I think when
you have receivers, if you're anything
about yourself, Tanner knows this, if
they got one-on-one with you, you're
going to be you should beat them. And I
think Jaden Dames will love that as
well. But, you know, the ultimate thing
is I just believe they have positioned
themselves so well to where there's a
lot of guys offensively and we'll get
into the defense later on that they
could pick and I would be thrilled with
it because there's so much talent out
there. It's been drafts where you look
at you got to get certain people,
>> but when you look at this draft, you
don't have to get a person. You got a
multitude of guys you can get and be
totally satisfied.
>> No doubt.
>> And we got to mention offensive line.
And I I hate to do it cuz I know the
chat probably killing me right now cuz
they're like no way we want to go
offensive line. However, we have seen AP
in the last two drafts go high with
offensive lineman Josh Connley Jr.
Brandon Coleman. Now we have addressed
the offensive line. We brought back a
guy in Chris Paul Tanner. Is there a
world where you see a offensive line
going to the commanders in the first
round?
>> You know I was always told never to say
never. So uh I don't know. I don't think
in a first round though. I don't think
this draft, you know, we going to lean
heavily on trying to use that pick for
offensive lineman in the first round. I
I will say that what what we were
talking about before we got on air is I
can see us probably getting some in the
later round, especially a center, you
know, knowing that we going to need help
there, you know. Um I have full
confidence in in Allegreti knowing that
he's going to be the guy for our center,
but I do believe it'll be great to bring
in some depth and bring in a guy who can
come in and probably play.
>> Man, so much to be excited about. A lot
of that has to do with how great AP and
DQ have drafted in these last few years.
Let's take a look at some of their
previous draft classes cuz there's
plenty of variety when it comes to Quinn
and Peters and how they drafted in 2025.
In the first round, offensive tackle
Josh Connelly Jr. went 29th overall,
followed by quarterback Trey Amos. Both
young men were starters when healthy.
And we can't forget
biggest steel of the 2025 draft and
seventh round pick Bill Kroski Merritt.
Another strong draft class for DQ and
AP. And once again, we found ourselves
in position to pick best available
because they knocked it out in free
agency. And earlier this week, our guy
Logan Paulson caught up with head coach
Dan Quinn to talk all about it. Let's
check it out.
>> Yeah, and I think that's interesting you
bring up like the relationship there
because you bring in all these, you
know, big- time pass rushers, big time
big time. How does the free agency
period affect what you're doing with the
draft and your philosophy heading in?
Like I think that's always a fun kind of
conversation to have.
>> It is. And anytime you can go and really
feel comfortable to go play before the
draft, we know you're really sitting in
a strong spot. And that's how we feel
today because you're not we have to get
this or we have to get that, we have to
get this. And so going into it, it
allows you um to add to the group. And
that's such a cool piece to it. But
yeah, we're really excited about the
people that we added. Different pieces,
some rushers, add a backer who's got
inside blitz techniques, some corners,
obviously a tight end with and, you
know, just different spots, running
back, you know, just different pieces to
how we'd go about it. And, uh,
>> we're able to resign some players, too,
which was a big deal for us. So, yeah,
we're excited with this group that we
have and then to add to it here in a
couple weeks. U, yeah, we're pumped for
that, too.
>> Yeah. And talking about bringing new
people in and you were always talking
about your growth mindset and how you
kind of always want to evolve and change
and be the best version of yourself. How
has that impacted the way you evaluate
these guys coming out? It's like such a
different game, such a different process
for you. Can you talk about some of that
for us? I
>> think you want to find out like from a
player standpoint, what are the unique
things that player can bring to the team
>> and can they find spaces to do that over
and over again? And so like for instance
in your spot for the
>> people like all right this guy could run
block better than most everybody but
that was that was your superpower and so
Mike and the staff here they they came
to find that out and recognize that and
then put you in the spots to allow you
to do your thing. Man I can get my
helmet wide and get run. I can knock
people out.
>> And so that type of skill
is really appreciated. And so as we're
going through the draft process, what
would the player do if they were here on
our team?
>> Who would they compete with? What would
that look like? How would we feature
them? Whether it's offense or defense.
And Larry Iso is a big part of the
evaluations, too. He goes through a lot
of their tape during college special
teams or just offensively and
defensively and how would they fit into
that role as well. And so when we put
all those together, that's why we love
the dialogue, you know, in terms of
getting ready for the draft.
Check out my game plan crew. Looking
good together. Now, it's just not the
Commanders with decisions to be made
tonight, fellas. Here is a look at how
the top 10 picks stand right now for
tonight's draft. You see the Raiders at
one, Jets at two, Cardinals at three.
But as we know with the draft, a lot of
things can shake. And speaking of things
shaking, our guys are out in Aspen right
now, ready to do a draft of their own.
Logan Paulson and London Fletcher are
making some decisions. That's why they
make the big bucks. Fellas, what you got
for the top 10?
>> Yeah.
>> All right, it's time for the 800th and
final and probably inaccurate mock draft
of the draft season and but you know,
maybe we're a little more on like closer
to the nose here with Logan and London.
>> We'll see, man.
>> How many How many players did you
evaluate this year?
>> Uh this year 175.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> 175. And uh how many of them could be
commanders this year at number seven?
>> Yeah, 48 of them have evaluated about
10.
>> Yeah, I was going to say it is 10.
>> 15 maybe.
>> Uh let's go through our mock draft. Uh
final mock draft. Uh the easiest thing
to do which everybody has known for
months and it's the only thing anything
that everyone's known for months is the
Raiders are going to take Fernand
Mendes.
>> Oh, do they know that? What's going to
happen?
>> That's about it, right? That's that's
the only I would bet on that. I I feel
pretty good about that.
>> You want a piece of trivia?
>> Sure. Okay. So, he's going to be the
highest drafted Indiana quarterback of
all time by far. Number one overall.
>> Do you know who the highest drafted
quarterback from Indiana was before
tonight?
>> Ind uh
>> and I'll give you a hint.
>> He played for the Washington Redskins.
>> I got this. Yeah.
>> Trent Gray.
>> No. Babe Laughenberg. Babe Laughenberg.
>> I was on the Babe Loftenberg. Sixth
round pick in 1983
quarterback before that.
>> Highest quarterback ever drafted out of
Indiana before tonight. Fernando
Mendoza. All right. So, no one has known
even up through this week what is going
to happen at number two. It's been
boiled down to a couple of names. Where
did you land on the Jets?
>> So, I think for me it's going to be
David Bailey here because like Fletch
and I talked about this like I think
David Bailey is a fantastic edge rusher.
14 sacks last year. Led the nation in
pressures, bunch of TFLs. Like he's an
explosive player and he's got the
length, he's got the weight, he's got
the get off, you know, four five type of
athlete there. And so I look at this and
I say to myself like this is exactly the
type of player that the New York Jets
Jets want here.
>> Yes. Yeah, absolutely. And there's a
question like, is it going to be Bailey?
Is it going to be Reese? I think when
you're looking at Ree, you're projecting
Baileyy's a much better pass rush off
the edge. You know, he's the he's the
given. You know what you're getting with
him. I don't feel like the Jets at
number two can take a gamble on on a a
project, so to speak.
>> I think the interesting thing is is the
coach can't, but maybe the GM can, you
know, and so I think that's that's where
it's one of those things where maybe the
GM says, "Hey, Arbell Reese." But again,
if I'm if Logan Pollson's the GM of the
Jets, I'd go David.
>> We've heard a lot of smoke throughout
the process, too, that Bailey or Ree,
but likely Bailey was someone the
Cowboys wanted. The Cowboys had been
floated as a trade partner for a lot of
people. So, I don't put it past if the
right deal came along that the Jets, who
are revamping everything, would move,
but it would take a pretty hefty pat.
>> Well, this is the fun thing I think
about the first five picks here is if he
goes to three, I know the Arizona
Cardinal want to trade back. That's I
know that for a fact, right? So if he
lines up here, I think heads up for the
Cowboys maybe there.
>> If somebody, you mentioned Arizona,
somebody potentially moving up.
>> Would somebody move up to take a running
back? Jeremiah Love, most people feel
like he's the best player in the draft,
but do you move up that high to take a
running back? Or are you moving up to
take either Reese or Bailey?
>> See, that's what I would say. I'd say
Reese Reese or Bailey, especially the
the Cowboys, if that's a team we're
talking about. They are looking for a
defensive stalworth, new defensive
coordinator. He wants to have more
varied fronts. Think about the
flexibility that Arbell Reese brings,
right? ball on ball. I can drop in a
coverage, right? And so that's one where
I'd kind of maybe maybe Arizona is able
to get out. They're not going to get
every dollar out of the trade, I don't
think. But I think that could be an
interesting spot for for had Dallas not
brought back Javvante Williams, I would
have thought maybe there's some kind of
They love stars. This is going to be a
massive star, have this long lineage of
star running backs there. But that
doesn't seem like a fit. If they're
going to move up, they're moving up for
one of these edges and they need
defensive
>> Exactly. That's what I was about to say.
When you look at the Dallas Cowboys,
what was their real Achilles heels last
year? their inability to get stops on
defense when they trade away Micah
Parsons. They had no pass rush at times
in ball games. They're going to score a
ton of points. They need difference
makers on the defense and particularly
they need guys in that p in that
defensive front who can get after the
quarterback. So, watch the watch for the
Dallas Cowboys to move up and take a
defensive play.
>> Yeah, very possible at the next couple
of Cleveland, Tennessee for sure. But
with love, you you looked at everybody.
Best player in the draft.
>> By far best player in the draft. I mean,
he just checks every box, height,
weight, speed, explosiveness, run
routes, good pass protector, and he's
kind of the opposite, honestly, of Arvel
Ree. Like Arvel Reese is this kind of
where are you going to play on ball, off
ball, but just kind of this super
athlete that's really physical. So to
me, I just can't get past taking a guy
with those physical traits here at four
for Salah and how he wants to play this
attacking style downhill. The other
name, Fletch,
>> who's the other name?
>> Is your Buckeye here? It's Sunny Style.
Sunny Style. Oh yeah, get your Fred
Warner in there
>> there. So if you think if you look at
Sunny and Arll, a lot of similar
similarities and traits.
>> Um both can play off ball uh rush the
edge versatility. I think for Arville
Reese,
>> he's the ideal three, four outside
linebacker,
>> which is not what Solid does.
>> Yeah. So and and really is Salah going
to be the one making that decision or is
this the GM? I know this is Salah's
defense, but is he
>> I will say this about him. If you got
some time today, you know, before the
draft starts, go check out YouTube and
watch him just hunt quarterbacks from
that spy spot. Exactly. And it kind of
makes your mouth water thinking about
what he could be as an edge rusher. You
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. That's why I say put him in a
three- four defense as an outside. You
get him a lot of times going against a
tight end. Get him on a on a on a a
running black back. So hopefully uh he
he ends up in the 34 defense.
>> Maybe the most versatile defensive
player who's an impact player out of the
board. They had him with 300 and
something snaps on the edge and 275
snaps as an offball linebacker. He can
do literally everything. So you can move
him around and do whatever you want. All
right. So that would look like a spot
where a trade potentially could occur.
This is also if they were to go Sunny
Styles that would make five really
interesting because if Reese is still
available and the Giants have Brian
Burns, Kavon Tibido, Abdul Carter, you
could make a case that that's not the
pick for them. They'd go in a different
direction. Then all of a sudden things
get really interesting.
>> Yeah, I think this is interesting. So,
when I first did this mock, it was
before they traded for DE before they
traded Dexter Lawrence, right? So, I
think now that Dexter Lawrence is gone,
I think they can now either get the
offensive lineman at 10, get a playmaker
here offensively or defensively.
>> Who do you like playmaker wise?
>> So, so to me, if if Sunny Styles goes
there to Tennessee,
>> and he doesn't go here. I think Sunny
Styles is here for them. I think it's um
uh Caleb DS or a receiver. And we've
been talking quite a lot about Jordan
could take the best receiver off of the
board, likely Jordan Tyson, and think
they're going to get a very, very good
defensive player at 10, Caleb DS, maybe
Delane, someone who slips down to number
10.
>> I think people might be surprised to
hear you say Jordan Tyson, and like
let's not get it twisted. Cardinal
Tate's a really good football player,
but Jordan Tyson on tape is the better
prospect
>> when when you look at is if we're
watching this tape sound down and you're
>> I'm Ohio State guy, but watching those
guys side by side,
>> Jordan Tyson just jumps off the off the
film, his explosiveness, ability to make
plays on all different levels, the
twitchiness, the uh run catch, break
tackles. Now, uh Tate doesn't do that
doesn't do that as much. Not as much run
after catch in terms of breaking tackle
stuff like that.
>> But can you imagine Malik Neighbors and
Jordan Tyson?
>> Scary thought.
>> Yeah. And it's going to change the
outlook I think if this is were to
happen. Here's CD Lamb George Pickkins
down in Dallas. Here's Neighbors and
Tyson in New York. And do you know what
Philadelphia AJ Brown or no AJ Brown you
know what the situation is with their
offense.
>> It screams where we're going to get to
at number seven where there's going to
be a definitive need on the defensive
side of the ball. But first comes
Cleveland who also feel like a massive
wild card in this.
>> So to me this is the trade spot. So I
put Kaden Proctor in here. He's the
tackle from Alabama. He's this is
>> that's too high for him.
>> So So that's I'm glad you brought that
up, right? Because I think what they
they're they're heavily analytics driven
in their department, right? So they want
tackles with length. They want a left
tackle. So Monroe Freeling Caleb Proctor
put that in here. But like you said,
Fletch, no one's going to take him this
high. They want to trade out of this
spot bad man. So if someone wants a
receiver, this is who they're going to
call. If if Sunny Styles slips, this is
going to call cuz I think if they're
picking at 12, this pick looks much more
reasonable in terms of trace the
offensive lineman here at six.
>> What about this? What if we move up one
spot to ensure
>> that Dallas doesn't come in here and try
to jump and and take Sunny Styles or you
mentioned I think you were leaning this
way a cornerback. That's right.
>> We we who we who are we taking who are
we taking at seven?
>> To me, it's come down to two people.
It's Caleb Downs or Mansort of Lane. I
think Mansor Lane would be the pick that
I think they're going to lead.
>> If Styles is off the board,
>> if Styles is off the board, that's
correct. And I think he's going to go
here to the uh to the New York Giants.
But Mans to me would be the pick here.
Um because I think he again I look at
the contract values of corners compared
to safeties. I look at the impact of a
premier state corner in this defense and
I say, man, that feels like maybe that's
the right fit there.
>> Man, if I look at this, if when you
think about Sunny Styles, I played with
his dad. um have kept in contact with
him, you know, over the last few years.
Sunonny is still just scratching the
surface as a middle linebacker, as a
linebacker. He was a safety, played
safety and then just only linebacker the
last two years. You see him a year ago
tape was okay. This year, I mean, he's
made tremendous.
>> How fun is he to watch, man?
>> Oh, and and still just me knowing the
position, having played it.
>> He there's so much meat on that bone.
>> So, yeah. I mean, he's one of my top two
players in this draft class. He he's a
fantastic football player. Yeah, Styles
would be amazing. Since we haven't had
we haven't had a London Fletcher in here
for a while, it' be nice to have a
London Fletcher back here in a while.
Delane, who Silver Spring native,
Archbishop Spalding, he not unlike Jaden
Daniels, started at Virginia Tech,
started at a different place, went to
LSU, and the game rose in such an
astronomical forum.
>> He gave up 165 yards in the SEC last
year. 165 in coverage. It really was
truly truly amazing. All right, that's
who London and Logan, that's where we
think we're going to be. Nobody seems to
really know. Let's uh say hi to our
friends at SeatGeek because it is time
for the best seat in the house. It is
presented by SeatGeek, the most
disruptive idea in ticketing. A ticket
that works. Expect the expected
SeatGeek. And let's send it back to our
friends in Pittsburgh.
Now, y'all looking good out in Ashford.
However, I do feel like we have the best
seat in the house cuz we are here in
Pittsburgh. Less than 20 minutes until
the draft time. Now, it was kind of hard
to hear, but it sounded like they were
saying either Sunny Styles or Mansour
Delane over there at number seven. So,
let's critique our guys a little bit.
Mansour Delane, LSU defensive back and
outside guy, the best defensive back in
this draft possibly. How do you see that
fitting here with what we have already?
Well, if you look at the three teams in
our division and you look at their
receivers,
>> it would be a great move
>> because if you going to have to compete
against teams that have legitimate pairs
of receivers on their football team, you
need to have defensive backs like that.
And Mansain has been a guy when you put
him on a guy, he can go out there and
handle them by himself. You look at Trey
Amos coming back. I think those two guys
will be great. He also signed some
people in the offseason, you know. I
think Mans Delane will be a great move
because of of the people we have to face
>> in our own division. And not only just
the people that we have to face, just
talking about the defense that we're
going to have now. And when you have a
strong set of guys on the outside like
that now, you don't have to worry about,
you know, what I'm showing up front. You
my coach talked about that in his
presser like, hey, it don't matter how
we get there. It don't matter what I
show you as long as we all get there.
So, think about it. Having two
bookenders and then say we got a we got
a a tough safety that we just brought in
and and then those guys up front, man,
doing the things that you saw those guys
do in Minnesota. Now we have that in our
backyard, man. I think it'll be
phenomenal.
>> And be when I look at a guy like Manor
Delane and how he would fit on this
team. You don't take a guy number seven
and say we're gonna move around. No,
we're gonna put him right on the
outside. So then we see Mikey possibly
go into that slot. We brought in a guy
name Robson who's also a slot corner.
It's got to be nice to have versatility
like that on your in your defensive back
field.
>> And think about it when you look at most
offenses in the league right now. It's
not just two receivers on the football
field. They have three. Sometimes they
have four wide. And if you have a
legitimate four uh defensive backs,
cornerbacks that can really play, Mikey
Mikey has proved what he could do
outside. I think last year going back
inside the NFL was a little different.
And receiver has a two-way go, but I
think he'll be much better at that this
year. But if you look at the fact that
if you go out there and get a man, you
have a Trey Amos, you have a Meek
Robinson, I mean, you also bring in and
you have Mikey there, you put you go out
there and try to put four receivers, you
have a advantage on the defense with
those type of guys.
>> It'll be a great problem to have. You
can never have too much talent or too
much help on any side of the ball. So,
it'll be a great problem to have for us.
>> And fellas, we got to see Logan and
London put their predictor hats on.
Y'all are going to do some predictions
right now. [__] I'll start with you.
Put you on the spot cuz I know you love
being on the spot. Number seven, who do
you think Washington's going with?
>> You know what? I I haven't finalized.
I've been pop jumping around with three
guys and I'm going to tell you why.
Okay. Cornell Tate, I think he really
fits with this football team. He can we
and I think when you start looking at
the receiver room you have to start
thinking about not just this year but
the years coming after I believe he
could come in and help us out man the
lane because a guy like that you can put
him on somebody's top receiver you can
put him on a second receiver and just
forget about it he's that he has that
type of talent and then the guy who I
absolutely love in this draft is Ruben
Bane Jr. This guy plays violently on the
football field. That's what I like to
see. If you're a defensive player, you
want to go out there and debo people.
And he did it time in and time out. And
I believe he could do the same thing at
the next level. If we giving all these
guys credit to be able to pass rush,
give him credit for being that violent.
That dude is strong. He if he pops you,
you going to bounce back. And I
absolutely love So one of those three
guys wouldn't make a problem to me.
>> So I'm going to be a little odd with
this one. you know, I I want to I want
to spice it up a little bit. I don't
have a guy, you know, potentially that
that I feel that would be best for that
pick,
>> but I do have a uh uh I guess you can
say what if what if we traded that pick
traded with it's three teams that I'm
looking at and I had the Dolphins cuz
they have two picks in the first round.
Uh I believe the the Jets and the
Browns.
>> All three of those teams, they got
nothing to do with our division. we
could probably possibly trade with them,
get them get them our early pick, take
their later pick and get their second
round pick for that trade. So that's
what I see and I will hope will happen.
But then again, we'll be working a
little longer tonight too if that
happens. So who knows me and Bish doing
a little sag cuz we like it's going to
be a long night for us if we end up with
a second round pick or later first round
pick, but it's all good. We are here for
the best fans in the NFL. This has been
the Command Center live draft night
special presented by Si. We are out here
in Pittsburgh. Shout out to our Get Loud
crew and all of our Commanders family
that are out at Northwest Stadium
partying up. We wish y'all were there.
We wish we were there with y'all. Swear
so hard with us as well. And our crew
out in Ashburg, baby, our radio crew.
Y'all look good out there, man. We've
had so much fun out here in Pittsburgh.
I am signing off. I'm your host Brian
Cob Jr. here with Brian Mitchell,
Santana Moss. Again, shout out Mike
Jinx, Fresh, Sean Springs, Graham
Weinstein, London Fletcher, and of
course the legend Logan Paul. My brother
LP will be back when the Commanders are
on the clock with the number seven pick.
We'll see y'all soon, baby.
Portions of the Command Center Draft
Night special were filmed at the Big
Bear.ai Command Center studio.
Bigbear.ai offers mission ready AI for a
rapidly evolving world, proudly
protecting the Washington Commanders and
its fans. Heat.
Heat.